- 干我吧，宝贝 - 当然
Yeah. Fuck me, baby. Yes, please.
喂？
Hello?
想找乐子吗？
Want to have a little fun?
你是谁？
Who is this?
你先说你的吧
Tell me your name,
我才不要
I'll tell you mine.
我不这样认为
I don't think so.
什么声音？
What's that noise?
我放屁了
I farted.
没想到你听得见
I didn't think you would hear me.
不，那噗噗的声音
No, that popping noise.
我在做爆米花
I'm making popcorn and
准备看片子
getting ready to watch a video.
什么片子？
What is it?
只是部恐怖片
It's just a scary movie.
你喜欢恐怖片吗？
Do you like scary movies?
你最喜欢那一部？
What's your favorite?
不知道
I don't know.
想想嘛
Think.
有了，是精灵也疯狂
I know! Kazaam.
侠客欧尼尔演精灵的那一部
You know, the one where Shaq plays a genie.
那不是恐怖片
That's not a horror movie.
那是你没看过欧尼尔的演技
Well, you haven't seen Shaq act.
你的声音很甜美
Hey, you have a nice voice.
谢了
Thanks.
你没告诉我你是谁
You never did tell me your name.
你为何想知道？
Why do you want to know my name?
我想知道我现在正在看的是谁
Because I want to know who I'm looking at.
你说什么？
What did you say?
大波霸
Nice breasts.
你想干嘛？
Look, what do you want?
我想看看你里面有没有料
I want to see what your insides look like.
那就翻到55页
Well, then, turn to page fifty-four.
好耶
Hey, nice.
混球，你闹够了
Listen, asshole, you've had your fun!
你最好就此打住
Now you'd better stop or else.
不然呢？
Or else what?
我男友随时会到
Or else my boyfriend's
他是黑人
going to be here any minute.
可以扁死你
And he's black and he'll kick your ass!
是吗？
Oh, really?
对
Yeah.
你是指打扮成女人的那个？
You mean the one who wears makeup and dresses like a woman?
你怎么知道？
How did you know?
把阳台的灯打开
Turn the porch lights on.
救命、救命
Help! Help!
不是他啦
That's not my boyfriend.
我不过就
I've fucked him a couple times,
跟他上过几次床而已
but that's it.
我要报警了
Look, I'm calling the cops!
去啊，去报警啊
Go ahead. Call the cops.
但你最好先查看一下后门
But you might want to check the back door first.
你忘了上锁了
You forgot to lock it.
接招吧，大变态
Take that, you psycho!
我的脚没知觉了
I can't feel my legs.
我的手断了
I think my arm is broken.
抱歉
Sorry.
我要跟我妈讲
I want my mommy.
你好，茱儿
Hello, Drew.
天啊
Oh, God.
“活路/死路”
SAFETY DEATH
不
No!
爸
Daddy!
爸，不、不...
Daddy, no! No!
什么声音？
Did you hear something?
我没听见什么声音
No, I didn't hear anything.
巴比，你干嘛？我爸就在隔壁
Bobby, what are you doing? My dad's in the other room!
我想起我从未从窗户爬进来过
It just occurred to me I never climbed through your window before.
现在你满足了吧，你快走吧
Yeah, well, now that you got it out of your system, Bobby, you have to leave!
为什么？
Why?
小心
Come on.
里面怎么了？
What's going on in there?
老爸的头卡住了
Daddy's head is stuck.
快松开
Unstick Daddy's head.
爸，拜托你先敲门嘛
Dad, can you knock?
敲门？
Knock?
我听见里面有人尖叫
I thought I heard screaming in here.
没有人尖叫啊
No, you didn't , Dad.
可能是我刚喀药的幻觉吧
It could have been that crack I smoked earlier, I guess.
没错
That's what it was.
我要离开镇上几天
I got to leave town for a couple days.
别担心
No big deal.
我跟那几个哥伦比亚人的生意
That new business I started with those Colombians - -
你是说艾斯可叔叔
You mean Uncle Escobar.
对
That's right.
出了问题
There's a problem.
有些钱不见了
Some money went missing.
看来有些人会完了
Apparently, some legs are going to get broken.
我最好还是躲个几天吧
It's just better if I lay low for a couple of days.
如果警察来查
Now if the cops raid the place.
我根本不认识你
I never heard of you.
别忘了
And don't forget.
湮灭证据
To flush your stash.
你真棒
You are my little girl.
我爱你...
I love you so much.
我在咖啡罐里留了点好料给你
...that I left you a little something in the coffee can.
卖之前记得要掺点料
But you have to remember to step on it before you sell it.
你要拿什么掺进去？
Now, what are you going to cut it with?
苏打...
Baking....
苏打粉，不是发粉
Baking soda. Not baking powder.
放发粉
Because baking powder guys
帅哥就会发了
will have muffins growing out of their nose.
你就喜欢这样
You love that joke,
对吧？
don't you, honey?
你两岁时就喜欢这样掺了
You've loved that joke since you were two years old.
好吧...
Okay, well...
我爱你
Okay, I love you.
I love you.
一路顺风
Have a good trip.
拜
Bye.
安全了？
Is the coast clear?
辛蒂，这件睡衣...
Cindy, that nightgown.
真惊险，天啊
That was close. God.
我本来在家看“大法师”
I was home watching The Exorcist.
那片子却让我想起你
And it got me thinking about you.
若你是想起我吐绿黏液
If this is about the time I puked green slime.
还用十字架自慰的那次
and masturbated with a crucifix...
那是我第一次参加饮酒大会
...it was my first keg party, Bobby.
不，不
No, no.
那是电视版
It was edited for TV.
精彩片段都剪了
All the good stuff was cut out.
那你是想爬上来跟我玩耍？
So you thought you would just climb through my window and play bump-bump?
我是希望有人能舔我蛋蛋
I was kind of hoping to get my balls licked...
但我决不会动你内裤
...but I wouldn't want to break
好吗？
your underwear rule, now, would I?
也许我能跟你隔着睡衣玩玩？
So maybe just some on-top-of-the-clothes type stuff?.
好吧，就一下子
Okay. But just for a minute.
搞什么...
What the...?
跑错场景了
Wrong set.
巴比，不要
No, Bobby, don't.
妈呀
Jeez.
“禁止入内”
NO TRESPASSING
是我爸
Yeah, my dad.
好了，大种马
Okay, stud.
你该走了
You have to go now.
关于上床的事
About the sex stuff. I was only half serious.
我并不想逼你
I mean, I don't want to rush you.
你接受辅导级的画面吗？
Would you settle for PG-thirteen?
什么？
What's that?
天啊
Oh, jeez.
晚安，巴比
Good night, Bobby.
矮子，你好吵
Shorty, you are so loud.
记得今天要去上课
And make sure you take your behind to class today.
我会去上课的
I do be going to class.
吃便当不叫上课
Lunch is not a class, Shorty.
偷吃零食总算吧
It is when you got the munchies.
看吧，你就是这么蠢
See, that's why you such a dumb-ass.
去你妈的
Your mother.
你是我弟，那也是你妈
You my brother.
对喔
That's your mother too, jackass.
那...你爸是猪头
Oh, yeah. Well, then, your father's stupid.
又怎样？我又不知他是谁
So? I don't know him.
是啊，我也是
Yeah, me neither.
辣妹，准备好了？
Hey, girl, you ready?
一会就好
Yeah, in a minute.
快点，我们迟到了
Come on, we'll be late.
等等，帕妃来了
Wait, there's Buffy.
你干嘛跟她混
I don't know why you hang out with her.
她是个贱货
She is such a ho.
你干嘛这样说？
Why do you say that?
因为我知道
Because I've seen her.
我朋友小席夏天开了泳池派对
My friend Sean had a pool party this summer.
你知道的，吹牛老爹
You know, Puff Daddy.
总之
Anyway,
大家都在喝法国香槟
everybody was drinking Crystal champagne.
接着大家都发疯
And then it started to get wild,
在池里乱搞
and people was getting freaky in the pool.
我看到
I look over and
她在按摩池跟男人乱搞
there was your girl getting buck-wild in the Jacuzzi.
那又怎样？
So?
对方是个伴舞的
With a backup dancer.
那真是没格调
I mean, that's nasty.
那比跟警卫搞还没品
That's lower than the security guard.
至少警卫能放你进场看演唱会
At least security can get you backstage.
她真不自爱
She don't love herself.
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得帕妃很甜美
I think Buffy's sweet, Brenda.
她假仙死了
She is as fake as Press-on nails
嘿，小甜甜
Hey, baby girl!
你好，好姐妹
What is up, my sister?
拜，吉先生
Bye, Mr. Gillmore.
他走了？
Is he gone?
对
Yep.
我喜欢这个颜色
I love this color.
让我看看
Let me see that.
你们不该用这个牌子
You guys should not use this brand.
为什么？
Why not?
他们拿产品在动物身上试验
Because they test their products on animals.
看过他们怎么对待那些动物吗
Look. Have you seen what they do to those poor animals?
“停止动物试验”
STOP ANIMAL TESTING!
我很关心大众
Well, I am much more of a people person.
我愿意接济世上饥贫的孩童
I'd like to feed all the hungry children of the world.
我宁可帮助人
I'd much rather help man than animal.
给我一元吧？
Spare a dollar?
滚远一点，脏鬼
Get away from me, you bum!
他只是饿了
Can't you see he's just hungry?
拿去吧
Here you go, sir.
这是三明治
A nice sandwich.
看到了吧？
See?
我要的是一元
I said a dollar, bitch!
天啊
God.
看看这地方
Look at this place.
真像马戏团大公演
It's a circus.
你们好，我是海盖儿
Hello, I'm Gail Hailstorm.
畅销书“你死我赚”的作者
Author of the book You're Dead, I'm rich.
一个小镇因一桩事故陷入恐慌
A small college town is in shock after the unthinkable has happened;
一位少女惨遭残酷谋杀
A brutal killing spree that left one teen dead- -
我受够了，两位青少年死亡...
That's it. Two teens dead...
这个小镇陷入混乱中
...and this small town shaken and stirred.
这种时刻...
It's times like these...
警方到处寻找线索
Police are combing the area for clues.
目前并未找到目击证人
There are no witnesses available at this time.
也没有逮捕嫌疑犯
There are no suspects in custody.
警方请求民众协助破案
Police are asking anyone to come forward.
黑人电台为您报导
Reporting live for Black TV;
白人死了
White folks are dead.
我们快走
We're getting the fuck out of there!
快落跑啊
Let's roll, Jack!
妈的，快收拾好，走啊
Fuck! Grab your shit and let's go.
你想媒体会访问我们吗？
Do you think the press will want to talk to us?
不，媒体只想访问最无知的人
No. The press only wants to interview the most ignorant person they can find.
我上电视了
I'm on TV!
上回是被捕时上的
Oh, shit! First cops, now this!
天啊，我会变成名人的
Oh, man, I'm going to be a star,
孩子
son!
请你谈谈遇害的茱儿
What can you tell us about Drew?
她的屁股真大
Well, she had the fat ass.
大辣妹
I mean it was like bang!
你跟她熟吗？
How close were you to the victim?
很熟
Real close.
强暴丸药效过后，她说要告我
Till the roofies wore off. Then she woke up, Talking about pressing charges...
所以我就不继续舔她屁屁了
...so I just pulled my tongue out of her ass and left.
你想对茱儿说什么？
What would have been your last words of Drew?
跑，贱货，快跑啊
Run, bitch, run!
兄弟
Hey, yo, dawg.
我这样穿像同志吗？
Does this shirt make me look gay?
不像
No, man.
现在呢？
What about now?
不像
No.
很好
Cool.
拿一张吧
Here, take one, guys!
别忘了周二投票
Don't forget; Election's Tuesday.
别忘了，周二投票
该死
Goddamn it!
他妈的旦旦面
Son of a bitch!
怎么了，宝贝？
What's the matter, honey?
我的成绩单
My report card.
“白痴”
DUMBASS
至少里面还有个A嘛
At least you got one A.
对喔，没错
Yeah, I did, huh?
你真聪明
You're so smart.
有看到巴比吗？
Has anybody seen Bobby?
没有
No. You know what?
那家伙老爱迟到
That kid is always late.
我真不懂
I don't get it.
他住的那么近
He lives so close.
回头见了
See you later.
老爸，老妈，吉姆
Hairy Mama, Bubba, Jim, Big Jim,
大小吉姆，瘦吉姆还有大家
Little Jim, Slim Jim, everyone.
拜了
I'll see you later.
小弟，回头见
Ciao, Ding. All right.
辣妹
Damn, girl.
我真想钻进你裤裆里
I'd sure like to get in your pants.
真的？
Really?
是啊，你穿几号的裤子？
Yeah. What size are these?
大家好
Hey, guys.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
你好吗？
How you feeling?
很好
Good.
有看到那些记者吗？
You guys see all the reporters out there?
听说辣妹茱儿昨晚被人杀了
Saying that girl Drew Decker got killed last night.
我想我认识她
You know what? I think I knew her.
真的？
Really?
对，她哥叫史提夫吧？
Yeah. She had a brother named Steve?
没错
Yeah.
留长发，樱桃小嘴，俏屁股？
Long hair, pretty little mouth, perfect ass?
是她没错
That was her.
不，我说的是史提夫
No, I was talking about Steve.
他到底发生什么事了？
What ever happened to him?
你们觉得她在整整一年后...
Do you guys think it's strange
被人谋杀
that she got killed...
跟我们杀了那人
...exactly one year after we...
有关系吗？
...you know, killed that guy?
那是意外
That was an accident.
是吗，格瑞？
Was it, Greg?
你看他们在搞什么鬼？
Would you look at what they're doing?
我们何时才能做那档事？
When are we going to do stuff like that?
总有一天吧
One day.
你喜欢吗？
You like that, baby?
喜欢，真特别
Yeah, that's different.
你喜欢
You like that?
我爽透了
Oh, I love that.
我喜欢你摸我屁屁
Oh, I love when you play with my ass.
我没摸你屁屁
I'm not playing with your ass.
小雷
Ray!
我弄错了
Oh, my bad.
拜托
Come on, man.
巴比，放点音乐吧
Bobby, put on some music.
等等
Hold on.
放这卷
Here, put this on.
真是棒呆了
That's the shit right here.
宝贝
Baby.
停
Stop.
怎么？
What? What?
这很经典呢
It's a classic.
听收音机吧
Tune is the radio.
怎么？那是我妈的
What? It's launder day.
搞什么...
The fuck is...?
过来
Come over here.
干嘛？
What?
再靠近一点
Just get a little closer to me.
你想跟我说什么？
Something you're going to tell me?
你干嘛？
What are you doing?
我只要你摸摸它，拜托
Just touch it. Come on.
摸一下就好
Just a little bit. Come on.
我就想要你这样
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
爽啊
Oh, my God.
糟糕
Shit!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
怎么回事？
What was that?
我想我们撞到东西了
I think we hit something.
天啊
Oh, man!
你看车子撞的
Bobby, look at my car, man!
我爸会发飙的
My dad's going to freak!
我没看到
I didn't see it.
它突然钻出来的
It came out of nowhere.
天啊，我们撞上一只靴子
Oh, my God! We hit a boot!
脚呢？
Where's the foot?!
不知道
I don't know.
搞什么...
Where the...?
尸体在那
It's a body!
妈的，他死了？
Oh, shit. Is he alive?
不知道
I don't know.
去看一下
Check it out.
我不要
I can't.
妈的
Shit!
我们得报警
We have to call the police.
不行
No way.
我不要坐牢
I ain't going to jail.
一定得报警
We have to!
知道少男被送进牢会怎样吗？
Do you know what they do to young boys in prison?
那些性饥渴的囚犯就等着你
Those sex-starved convicts just waiting for a fresh piece of meat. You're right, Cindy.
也许我们该报警
Maybe we should call the police.
真好啊，小雷
That's a great idea, Ray.
布兰妲呢？
But what about Brenda?
你以为她想坐牢？
You think she wants to go to jail?
这是过失杀人
It's manslaughter.
我们死定了
We'll fry for this.
等着被关十到十五年吧
We're looking at 1 0 to 1 5 years.
闭嘴，巴比
Shut up, Bobby!
满身酒味...
Alcohol all over...
我没事
I'm fine.
麻烦大了
We're in so much trouble.
我没事
It's fine.
别想把责任推给我
And don't blame that shit on me, Ray.
天啊，我们得毁尸灭迹
Look, we'll get rid of the body.
不需要
Unnecessary.
你终于动脑袋了
Now you're thinking.
把他丢进海里
We'll dump him in the ocean.
丢码头边
Not the ocean, the pier.
我马上走
I'll be leaving now.
好主意
That's a great idea.
酒呢？
What about the alcohol?
丢了它
We'll get rid of it.
不会有问题的
It'll be all right.
没错
Absolutely.
动手吧
Come on. Let's go.
把他塞进后车厢
Put him in the trunk.
我不想跟这件事有关连
I won't have anything to do with this.
闭嘴
Shut up!
辛蒂，拜托
Cindy, come on.
我们就假装什么都没发生过
We'll just pretend it never happened.
就像我们喝醉乱搞那次一样
You know, like the time we got drunk and we went down on each other.
我抓他的手
I'll get his arm.
我抓其他只手
I'll grab his other arm.
我抓他屁屁
I'll grab his ass.
我们把他丢到威森湾里
We'll take him to Williamson Cove and dump him in there.
鲨鱼会帮我们料理他
The sharks'll take care of the evidence.
天啊，有人来了
God, someone's coming.
该死，是矮子
Oh, shit. It's Shorty.
布兰妲，搞定他
Brenda, take care of him.
矮子，你一定是无照驾驶
Shorty, I know you ain't driving
我有
without no papers.
我罩子亮着呢
I got papers, blunts, bongs...
还有令人精神振奋的好料
...all the ingredients to make a high nigga pie.
你在这干嘛？
Yo, can I help you?
小雷啊？
Yo, what's up, Ray?
需要接电吗？
Yo, son, you all need jumper cables?
不，不用
No, we're cool.
很好，反正我也没带
Good, I left my roach clip at home.
回家去，矮子
Go home, Shorty.
回头见
I'll see you later.
拜了，小雷
Peace, Ray.
把后车厢关上
Get the trunk closed.
关不起来
It won't close.
我来
I'll do it.
拜托
Hey! Come on!
等等，把他放下
Hold on. Put him down.
他真重.天啊
He's heavr. Oh, God.
好，听着
Jesus. Okay, look.
数到三就把他丢下去
On three we dump him over the ledge.
等等
Wait.
检查一下他的皮夹吧
Shouldn't we at least check his wallet?
干嘛？
For what?
他也许有钱呢
Shit, he might have some money.
我们已杀了他
We already committed murder.
就顺便抢他吧
We might as well rob his ass.
我拿信用卡
I'll take the credit cards.
我要珠宝
I want his jewelry.
我要他的内裤
I'll take his drawers.
放手...
Get off!. Hey, y'all, get off.
他的内裤是我的
His drawers are mine.
我拿到金戒指了
I got me a gold ring.
信用卡
Credit cards.
把他丢进水里吧
Let's get him in the water.
我做不到
I don't think I can, Greg.
现在还不迟
It's not too late.
闭嘴好吗？
Shut up, okay?!
天啊，我动手
Christ, already. I'll do it.
把他丢进水里就好，好吗？
Just get him into the water. Okay?
一，二...
One, two...
三
...three.
现在，我们达成协议
Right now, we make a pact.
一辈子都谨守秘密
We take this to our grave.
同意？
Agreed?
同意
Agreed.
说啊，辛蒂
Say it, Cindy.
说啊
Say it!
一辈子谨守秘密
We take this to our grave!
说啊，一辈子都谨守秘密
Say it! We take this to our grave!
说啊
Say it!
格瑞，冷静
Greg, chill.
一辈子谨守秘密，格瑞
We take this to our grave, Greg.
我们绝口不提
And we never mention this again.
不提什么？
Mention what?
我们刚杀了一个人
The guy we just killed.
你刚刚就提了
Well, you just mentioned it, Greg.
从现在开始算
Starting now!
真是个蠢妞
Stupid bitch, man.
我恨他
God, I hate him.
不会有事的，宝贝
It's going to be okay, baby.
不会有事的
It's going to be okay.
我保证
I promise.
再摸一次
Just touch it again.
拜托
Come on. Please.
一切都已过去了，辛蒂
You have to move on, Cindy.
一切都已过去了
That's all behind us now.
没错
Exactly.
这是巧合
It's a coincidence.
格瑞说的对
Greg's right.
你以为我们在演恐怖片吗？
I mean, what do you think we're in A horror movie?
你们说的对
You guys are right.
如果是的话...
If we were...
也许演我的人会是个大波霸
...they'd probably cast some dingbat like Jennifer Love Huge Tits to play me.
也许会找三十岁的老演员来演
Or they'd cast people in their late twenties, early thirties to play us.
摄影机准备
Kenny, get the camera ready.
把我口香糖收好
Here, hold my gum.
警长，请您讲几句话
Sheriff, can I get a statement?
无可奉告
No comment.
该死
Damn.
我跟谁搞才弄得到内幕消息？
Who do I have to screw around here to get a stupid story?
别乱跑
Hey, no running.
笨蛋
Loser.
慢慢走
Slow it down.
咬我啊
Blow me.
好吧
All right.
我是新闻前线采访记者海盖儿
Gale Hailstorm. Field reporter, Hard Story.
特别警探阿呆
Special Officer Doofy.
阿呆
Oh, hi, Doofy. Listen.
校园里出了什么事？
Is there a problem on campus?
无可奉告
No comment. No comment.
好吧
Okay. Okay.
你真是个年轻有为的警探
You know, you look awfully young to be a police officer.
我二十五岁半了
I'm twenty-five and a half years old.
就这么大
That's this many.
真大
So big.
对，很大了
Yeah. That's big.
你看来不过才十二岁
You don't look a day over twelve.
但你的眼神可锐利了
Except for the big head and glazed-over look in your eyes.
那是口水吗？
Ooh, is that drool?
对，我忘了吞下去了
Yeah, I forgot to swallow.
别担心
Don't worry,
我不会忘的
because I never forget.
提醒我别再搔你了
Remind me not to do that again.
抱歉
Sorry.
针对这场悲剧
Due to the recent tragedy,
警长和我...
the sheriff and me, your principal...
会开始询问所有的学生
...will be questioning all students throughout the day.
看来似乎是有个连续杀人犯
Sounds like we have a serial killer on our hands.
我不能说
I'm not supposed to say.
这是警方事务
It's official police business.
阿呆，你和我一起去车里...
Doofy, what do you say you and I go inside my van over there...
互相认识一下吧？
...and get to know each other better? Would you like that?
车里？
That van?
对，就是那辆车
Yeah, that van right there.
好吧，我们走
Yeah, okay. Let's go.
走吧
Come on.
这真是桩可怕的悲剧
A terrible tragedy and an unbearable loss.
在这样的日子里我们需要祷告
It's days like today that we need prayer in school.
它已侵蚀我们的信念
It starts to unravel the very moral fabric of our society.
好了
Here you go, baby.
去找你爸吧
You go to your daddy.
下课后见
I'll see you after class.
好了，同学们
Okay, class.
谁要先报告？
Who would like to give their oral presentation first?
谁？
Anybody?
还有谁？
Anybody else?
好吧，希瑟
Okay, Heather.
可以开始了吗？
Okay. Can I start?
我要报告的是第一修正案
My presentation is on the First Amendment.
这是1787年5月25日
And it began on May 25 th,
华盛顿在费城推动的
1 787 in Philly with George Washington.
记录上说
And it states, and I quote;
“我们的国父...”
''When our founding fathers...''
“争论我国宪法的变迁”
''...argued the passage of our glorious Constitution...''
“我知道去年万圣节的事”
I KNO W WHAT YOU DID LAST HALLO WEEN!
不对
NO BITCH!
我是指你们杀了人
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE GUY YOU KILLED!
第一修正案给我们言论自由
And so the First Amendment gives us the right to say what we want.
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
下一个是谁？
So, who's next?
坎辛蒂
Cindy Campbell.
她是那个...
Isn't she the daughter of,
谁的女儿吗？
well, you know?
对，就是她
Yeah, you mean old Mrs...
性感的...
Old Mrs...
对，唯一的...
Yeah, the one and only...
独一无二的
The one and only.
你好，辛蒂
Why, hello, Cindy.
校长好
Hi, Principal Squiggman.
谢了，阿呆
Thanks, Doofy.
我今天是特别警探阿呆
It's Special Officer Doofy today, Cind.
警长有些问题想问你
Sheriff has some questions he'd like to ask you today.
什么鬼味道？
What is that God-awful smell?
不知道
I don't know.
我大便了
I got a poopie.
你是说...
Did you just say
你拉在裤子上了
that you got poopie?
是啊，感觉很棒
Yeah. It was good.
叫他出去
Get him out of here.
谢谢你，阿呆
Thank you, Doofy.
你该回特殊教育班上课了
You should now go back to Special Ed.
好，敬礼
Okay. Salute.
顺便换条内裤吧
Maybe a change of underwear, son.
拜，阿呆
Bye, Doofy.
拜，辛蒂
Bye, Cind.
你好吗，辛蒂？
How are you, Cindy?
很好
Fine.
你呢，警长？
How are you, sheriff?.
发福又便秘
Bloated, constipated.
屁股上还长了疮
Got a boil on my ass the size of a walnut.
跟以往一样
You know, the usual.
辛蒂，我想问你一些茱儿的事
Cindy, I want to ask you some question about Drew Decker.
我跟她不熟
I didn't really know her.
拜托
Oh, come on.
你很熟的
Sure you do.
不
No, I mean,
我跟她真的不熟
I didn't really know her.
少来了
Been in this game a long time.
别跟我打混
Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
谈谈茱儿吧
Tell me about Drew.
她在床上是什么样子？
What was she like in bed, Cindy?
只是捉弄你一下
Tried to get you.
警察就喜欢这样
It's an old police trick.
你不会被骗
You didn't fall for it.
很好
Good for you.
传球，传球
Pass. Pass.
好，洗澡了
All right, shower up!
好耶
Yes!
小杜，打的好
Yo, Dugan, man, nice play.
够赞！
Word up.
强森，阻挡的好
Johnson, what a block, baby.
小伍，好屁股
Woodward, nice ass.
妈的
Damn.
格瑞
Yo, Greg,
你要去冲澡吗？
you going to hit the showers or what?
不，我要去打沙包
No, man. I think I'll work out.
运动一下
You know, beat the bag a little.
随你便，好吧
Suit yourself, kid. All right.
最后冲澡的是大笨蛋
Last one in the shower's a rotten egg.
快啊
Come on.
我要痛扁你们罗
Come on. I'm going to get you all.
别让雷叔叔逮到你了
Don't let Uncle Ray catch you.
“我都知道”
I KNO W!
这是谁干的？
Who did this?!
你在哪？
Where are you?!
这不好玩
This isn't funny, all right?!
鸡鸡这么小，可以算残障了
A small dick's like a disability, man!
你怎么可以欺负残障同胞
Would you make fun of a guy in a wheel chair?! Would you?!
出来，你这个大变态
Come on out here, you dick fuck!
我要打的你满地找牙
I'll kick the shit out of you right now!All right?!
大小不重要
It's not the size of the hammer.
重要的是好不好用
It's the nail you're throwing it at!
她死了真可惜
It's a shame how she died, you know.
她是个好女孩
She was such a nice girl.
是啊
Yeah.
她照顾过我弟阿呆
She used to babysit my brother, Doofy.
他爱死她了
He had the biggest crush on her.
小雷，你死定了
Ray, you're a dead man.
怎么？
What?
想光着身子摔角？
You want to get buck-naked and wrestle?
来吧
Bring it on, Ray.
帮我拿耳环
Hold my earrings.
润滑剂呢？
Where's my Vaseline?
别激动
Take it easy.
怎么回事？
What's the problem?
我拿给你看
I'll show you.
这是你？
That's you?
那时候热水没了，我冲冷水
They turned the hot water off in the shower,all right?
我的妈
Oh, fuck.
天啊
Oh, shit.
笑吧
Laugh it up, you guys.
笑大声点
Big laugh.
你们都去死吧
You can all go to hell.
不是只有你这样
You're not the only one who got one.
怎么？
What?
巴比也一样小？
You mean Bobby's got a baby dick too?
不，我是说收到警告
No, I was talking about the note.
我也收到了
I got one too.
有人知道
Somebody knows.
不可能
That's bullshit, Cindy.
有人想搞我们
Someone's just trying to fuck with us.
我们得报警
We have to call the police, Greg.
你报警
You call the police,
我就宰了你
and I'll kill you myself.
你伤到她了
You're hurting her, man.
你们最好都注意点
That goes for all of you guys.
那变态想杀我
That psycho wants a piece of me,
那就来吧
bring it on.
我才不要去坐牢
But I'm not going to jail.
懂吗？
You got that?
大家在说什么？
What's everybody talking about?
算了，矮子
Just forget it, Shorty.
你知道太多了
You already know too much.
“妙龄小姐选拔”
Teen Beauty Pageant
棒透了
Aren't they beautiful?
一号参赛者
Contestant number one.
很好
Very good.
二号参赛者
And contestant number two.
很好
Very good.
三号参赛者
And contestant number three.
那是我马子
That's my girl!
That's my girlfriend!
那也是我马子
Yeah, that's my girlfriend too!
去死吧
Hey, kiss my ass!
我也跟她搞过
Yeah, I'm hitting that too.
好耶，帕妃
All right, Buffy.
闭上你的鸟嘴
Shut the hell up.
她可火辣了
Yeah, man. Best pussy I ever had.
怎么？想打架？
What? You want a piece of me?
现在进行才艺比赛
Now the talent portion of the competition.
我要去楼下看
I'm going to go downstairs for a closer seat.
三号参赛者
Contestant number three...
吉帕妃
...Buffy Gilmore.
我要上厕所
I'm going to hit the head.
想喝什么吗？
You want anything?
不用，快回来
I'm good. But hurry back.
她要表演了
She's going to perform.
马上回来
Don't worry. I'll be back.
晚安，帕妃
Good evening, Buffy.
你要表演什么才艺？
What will be your talent for this evening?
演戏，我要演戏
Acting. I'll be doing a dramatic reading.
吉帕妃要演戏
Buffy Gilmore doing a dramatic reading.
演海滩游侠的桥段
Do that thing from Baywatch! She's running down the beach.
“喇叭小姐”
Miss Fellatio.
小心背后
Look out, Greg!
格瑞
Look behind you!
是他，是凶手
It's him! It's the killer!
天啊
Oh, my God!
快救命啊
Somebody do something!
快来人救命啊
Somebody do something
他会杀了他
He's killing him!
真有创意
Must be an original piece.
他在追杀他
He's killing him!
她不错
She's good.
她很棒
She's great.
你们是怎么回事？
What's wrong with you people?
太好了
That's fantastic.
你们为何不去救他？
You fucking bastards! Why won't anyone help!?
真棒
Amazing.
她是下一个性感巨星
She's the next Pamela Lee.
天啊，住手
Oh, God. Don't.
格瑞，撑着点
Greg, hold on!
请为帕妃鼓掌，太棒了
Give it up for Buffy Gilmore.
真是精彩
Wonderful.
冠军已经诞生
Absolutely fantastic.
帕妃小姐
We have a winner, ladies and gentlemen.
帕妃
Miss Buffy Gilmore.
等等
Buffy, wait.
你得回台上去
You have to go back onstage.
不，我得去找格瑞
No, I have to get to Greg.
你赢了
You won.
他们在叫你
They're calling your name.
外面有凶手
There's a killer.
赢了？
I won?
他们在叫你，快去
They're calling your name. Go.
怎么回事？
What happened?
格瑞呢？
What about Greg?
管他的，我赢了
Fuck Greg, I won.
恭喜
Congratulations.
滚开，输家
Out of my way, loser.
帕妃小姐
Miss Buffy Gilmore.
她来了，妙龄小姐
Here she comes, Miss Teen.
她棒极了
She's so fine.
大波霸
Such lovely tits.
把后冠给我，贱人
Give me my crown, bitch.
还有翘臀
And a great behind.
她在这里
There she is.
随时能让你上
Doggy style anytime.
我要从背后来
And I'll do her behind.
背后
Behind.
从背后
And behind.
就是她
There she is.
她喜欢玩六九式
She loves sixty-nine.
到处都找不到他
There's no sign of him anywhere.
他可能把尸体弄走了
He could've taken the body.
不可能
That's impossible.
没血迹
There's no blood.
什么都没有
There's nothing. Look around.
我想格瑞只是开玩笑
I bet it's just Greg playing another one of his dumb jokes.
一定找得到他
He'll turn up. I'm sure of it.
他也许正在我家等我们呢
He's probably at my house Waiting for us right now.
好吧
All right, fine.
但我还要到处找看看
But I'm going to look around some more.
你跟帕妃回家吧？
You mind going back home with Buffy?
好
No problem.
好吧
All right, fine.
打电话给我
Call me later.
喂？
Hello?
辛蒂
Hello, cindy.
你是谁？
Who is this?
是我巴比
It's me, Bobby.
你男友
You know, your boyfriend.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想我太紧张了
I guess I'm a little jumpy lately.
找到格瑞了？
Hey, any sign of Greg?
没有
No.
你要我过去吗？
Do you want me to come by?
不用
No.
我正在洗澡
I'm going to take a bath,
之后就要睡了
and then I'm going to bed.
好吧，我真的很想见你
Okay. I'd really like to se you,
不过...我爱你
but, I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too, baby.
巴比，我说过了
Bobby, I told you.
我知道你去年万圣节干的好事
I still know what you did last Halloween.
你是谁？
Who is this?
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
砍死你
I'm going to slice you up.
你是谁？
Who is this?
我会把你剁碎
I'm going to chop you like liver.
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
我就在屋里
I'm in the house.
知道我在哪吗？
Do you know where I am?
可能是任何角落
I could be anywhere.
我快如闪电
I'm like the wind , baby.
我在哪里？
Where am I?
你在沙发后面
You're behind the couch.
什么？你怎么知道？
What? How do you know that?
我看得到你的脚
I can see your feet.
好吧，转身
Okay, turn around.
闭上眼睛，不准偷看
Close your eyes. No peeking.
好耶，不，不对
Yeah. No. No, no.
不准偷看，转过去
No peeking. Turn around.
很好
Good.
好，找找看
Okay, now you look.
现在你不知道我在哪里了吧？
Now do you know where I am? You don't.
杀手先生
No, Mr. Killer,
我不知道
I don't know where you are.
告诉你吧
I'll give you a big clue.
我该戒酒了
I got to stop drinking.
奶奶
Grandma.
我的腰
Oh, my hip.
“119，出了什么事”
SHERIFF 91 1 What is your emergency?
白人女性有麻烦
White woman in trouble!
744公路有白人女性出事了
White woman in trouble off the 7 44- -
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
我听到尖叫
I heard screaming.
怎么了？
What's going on?
他刚才在这里
He was here.
就是凶手，巴比
The killer was here, Bobby.
没事了
It's okay.
我能解释
I can explain that.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
有个朋友给我的
A friend gave them to me.
辛蒂，辛蒂
Cindy! Cindy!
辛蒂
Cindy!
是我，辛蒂
It's me, Cind.
辛蒂，你了解我的
Cindy, you know me. Cindy.
我知道你很难过
I know you've had a rough night,
我不耽误你
so I won't keep you.
我想请你看几张照片
I just want you to look at some photos.Tell me what you think.
不？
No?
不
No.
抱歉，警长
I'm sorry, sheriff.
你确定？
You sure?
好吧，你可以走了
Okay, you're free to go.
有人送你吗？
Do you have somebody picking you up?
好吧...
All right. Oh, just...
再看一张吧
...just check on out again.
不行？
No?
好吧
All right. Well, worth a shot.
不喜欢就算了
All right, thanks.
你猜我跟逮到的妓女做了什么
Guess what I did with the hookers we busted?
不会吧
No way.
没错
All the way, man! Yes.
你看着
Watch this.
过来
Come on.
特别警探阿呆报到
Special Officer Doofy reporting.
阿呆，闻闻我的手指
Doofy, smell my fingers.
那是什么？
What's that?
等你成了男人就知道了
That's when you know You've become a man, Doofy!
泰瑞，闻闻我的手指
Terry. Smell my finger.
那是什么鬼味道？
What the hell is that?
我的屁眼
My ass.
快滚吧
Get the hell out of here.
妈说现在回家
Mom said get home now.
告诉妈我在忙着扮警察
Tell Mom I'm on official police business.
辛蒂，你还好吧？
Cindy, are you okay?
不准跟证人交谈
No talking to the witness.
去开车
Go to the car.
她跟我们走
She's coming with us.
妈知道吗？
Does Mom know?
知道
Yeah, Doofus.
妈说我戴徽章
Mom says when I wear this badge,
你就得尊敬我
you have to treat me like a man of the law.
妈也叫你别用吸尘器吸小弟弟
Mom also said for you to stop sticking your dick in the vacuum cleaner.
“警察局，2017年成立”
SHERIFF'S DEPT. FOUNEDE 201 7
三，二...
Three, two- -
不
Oh, no.
该死
Gosh darn.
又怎么了？
What now?
这些数字...
There's all these numbers- -
怎么？你不会算术？
What? Can't you count?
那简单
I'll make it easy for you.
肥猪，仔细听我说
Chubzilla, listen up, okay?
这只小猪去了市场
This little piggy went to the market.
这只小猪留在家里
This little piggy stayed home.
要是这只猪不拍摄
If this piggy doesn't roll the goddamn camera...
我就踢他屁股...
...I'll put my foot up his fucking- - -
现场播出了
We're live, Gail.
海盖儿在警局外...
Gail Hailstorm standing outside the police station...
我们正设法找到坎辛蒂
...where I'll try and get a glimpse of Cindy Campbell...
她今晚稍早遭受攻击
...the young girl who was attacked earlier this evening.
你踩到我了，猪头
You're on my foot, fat shit!
我是怎么说的？
What did I say?
别踩到盖儿的鞋
''Don't ever step on Gail's shoes.''
为什么？
Why not?!
因为盖儿穿名牌鞋
Because Gail wears Prada shoes.
你这个猪头
You idiot.
我很皮的
I'm a bad man.
辛蒂，请说句话吧
Cindy, can we get a statement?
我是妙龄小姐
Buffy Gilmore, Miss Teen.
她不想说
She's not talking.
警方有扣留任何人吗？
Do the police have someone in custody?
走吧，辛蒂
Come on, Cindy.
你屁股真肥
Your ass looks fat!
贱人
Bitch!
打的好
Nice shot.
走吧
Come on.
谁摸我？
Who copped a feel?
是我
Gail, it was me.
这是意外
It was an accident, Gail.
我只是摸了乳尖
I only touched it, the top of the breast.
真是柔软...
It was so tender and juicy- -
闭嘴
Shut up!!
矮子
Hello, Shorty.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
没什么，我在看比赛
Nothing. Sitting here watching the game.
哈些草
Smoking some bud.
你一个人吗？
Are you all alone?
大家好
What's up?!
搞什么？那是谁？
What the...? Who's that?
听电话
Yo, pick up the phone.
你好
What's up?!
What's up?
小杜，听电话
Yo, Dookie! Pick up the phone!
干嘛？
What's up?
你呢？
What are you doing, son?
没什么，到处砍人罗
Nothing. Just chilling, killing.
很好，很好
True, true.
是巴比吗？
You think Bobby did it?
不知道
I don't know.
但他在场
But he was there, Buffy.
我就知道他有问题
I knew there had to be something.
他太完美了
He's just too perfect.
英俊，聪明，又很能“干”
Handsome, smart, good in bed.
你说什么？
What did you say?
辛蒂
Hey, Cind.
冰敷袋来了
Got your ice pack for your hand.
抱歉
Sorry.
我再拿一个来敷头
I'll get you one for your head.
不用了，阿呆
No, that's okay, Doofy.
我们去逮你们丢进水里的人吧
We're going to get that guy you dumped in the water.
我就在隔壁
I'll be next door if you need me.
晚安，辛蒂
Night, Cind.
你告诉他了？
Buffy, you told him?
那白痴听见我跟格瑞交谈
The moron overheard a conversation Greg and I were having.
万一他说出去怎么办？
What if he says something?
谁会相信他？
Who'll believe a retarded retard like him anyway?
别担心
Don't worry.
辛蒂，电话
Cindy, telephone.
喂？
Hello?
辛蒂，你好
Hello, Cindy.
你猜怎么着？
Guess what?
你们逮错人了
You got the wrong guy.
不是巴比
It's not Bobby.
阿呆
Doofy!
不是他
No, it isn't.
你是谁？
Who is this?
喂？
Hello?
说过我清理房间时别来烦我的
I said don't disturb me while I'm cleaning my room!
听说巴比今早获释了
I heard Bobby got out this morning.
我没看到他
I haven't seen him around.
他生气吗？
Is he pissed?
你是说你诬指他是凶手？
You mean since you branded him the Candyman?
不，他伤心死了
No, his heart is broken.
这场景有点似曾相识呢
Yo, son. It's like I seen this all before.
你以前的学校有杀手？
They had a killer at your old school?
不，很像“惊声尖叫”
No, it was in this movie Scream. Same dialogue and everything.
真糟糕
This is ill.
结局怎样？
How did it end?
不知道
I don't know.
有黑鬼在电影院里火拼
Some niggas started shooing up in the movie theater,
没错
so we just broke out. No doubt.
好吧，今晚到我家集合
Okay, I say we all just stick together. Tonight everyone meet at my house.
带些朋友来
And bring some friends.
别四处张扬
But don't tell everyone, okay?
口风紧一点
Try to keep it quiet.
辛蒂家开派对
Party at Cindy's house!
大家有得乱搞了
Drunk white women for everybody!
要是看到巴比，跟他说我爱他
If you see Bobby, tell him I love him.
好
Okay. If I see Bobby,
我会说我爱他
I'll tell him I love him.
天啊
Jesus.
没关系，是我，宝贝
It's all right, it's just me, baby.
你还认为是我？
You don't still think it's me?
不
No.
但的确有人想杀我
But somebody did try to kill me.
警方说我吓跑他了
And the police said I scared him away.
我知道
I know.
他昨晚打电话给我
He called me last night.
看吧，不可能是我
You see, it couldn't have been me.
我被关着
I was in jail last night.
你真行
You're the best.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
请你体谅
Please understand.
体谅你把我当成凶手？
Understand that you'd rather call me a killer than touch me?
不是的
That's not true.
那你是怎么了？
Then what is it? What is it?
她走了，她不会再回来了
She's gone and she's not coming back!
已经一年多了，辛蒂
It's been over a year, Cindy.
但辣妹合唱团不能没有她
But Ginger was such an important part of the Spice Girls.
日子还是要过的
You got to move on, baby.
抱歉我的生活太复杂了
I'm sorry if my complicated life...
这对你实在不公平
...is an inconvenience to your perfect existence.
大家听清楚了
Okay, everybody, listen up.
我这么说吧...
Let me just say...
这些青少年被杀，实在是悲剧
...the killing of these teenagers has been tragic,
坏事总是年年有
but...you know, shit happens.
警长，警长
Sheriff!. Sheriff!.
是的，找碴小姐
Yes, Miss Thunderstorm.
找到辛蒂的父亲了吗？
Have they found Cindy Campbell's father?
他不是嫌犯？
Isn't he a suspect?
这是机密
That is classified information.
你怎么知道？
Where are you getting that?
抱歉
I'm sorry,
我不能透露资讯来源
but my sources are strictly confidential,sheriff.
嗨，盖儿
Hey, Gail.
盖儿爱吃小弟弟
Gail swallows.
看着.是谁？
Who is this?
什么？
What?
你想杀我？
You want to kill me?
等等
Oh, God. Hold on.
辛蒂，找你的
Cindy, it's for you.
别捉弄辛蒂了，帕妃
All right, knock it off, Buffy.
你们都听说过...
Now, as you all have heard...
镇上有凶手
...a killer is in town
警方给了我们一些安全准则
and the police have asked us to give you safety tips;
待在灯光明亮的地方
Stay in well-lit areas.
不要单独旅行
Do not travel alone whenever possible.
卫生纸由前往后擦
Always wipe front to back.
记住...
And remember;
千万不要相信别人
Never, ever believe someone...
尤其是想帮你刮毛的人
...who says that shaving your pubic hair will rid you of crab infestation.
我知道你们很难过
Now, I understand this is a difficult time for you young ladies.
如果有人想找我谈
So if anyone needs to come to my office to talk...
到办公室找我
...I am here for you.
一堆屁话
What a crock of shit.
才不是呢
It's not, Buffy!
他是当真的
He's real!
木兰老师？
Miss Mann?
请进
Come in, dear.
请坐
Have a seat.
把胸罩脱了吧
Take off your bra if you'd like.
不，谢了
No, thanks.
需要我帮忙吗？
What can I do for you, Cindy?
我需要谈谈
I need to talk.
我有个问题
See, I have this problem...
我不知该跟谁说
...and I don't know who to tell.
感觉很不清爽？
Not feeling so fresh?
阴道发痒？
Feminine odor and itching got you down?
不，不是的
No, not that.
那是什么？
Then what is it?
我有个恐怖的秘密
I have a terrible secret.
人都有秘密的
Well, we all have our little secret.
有时我们会做些不光彩的事
Sometimes we do things we're not proud of.
有些人为钱
Some for money...
有些人是为了测试自己的极限
...others to gain the athletic edge on them
这些秘密有时会反噬我们
Sometimes those secrets come back to haunt.
知道我的意思吗？
Do you know what I mean?
我知道
Yes, I do, Miss Mann.
谢谢蛋蛋...
Thanks for ball....
我是指，你的协助
I mean, all your help.
我得去上课了
I have to go to class.
随时欢迎你
Anytime, dear.
帕妃，要来吗？
Buffy, are you coming?
我马上到
I'll catch up with you guys in a sec.
死神到了
Redrum.
你好？
Hello?
有人吗？
Somebody there?
你好？
Hello?
真可笑
Very funny.
谁叫你打扮成这样？辛蒂？
Who put you up to this? Cindy?
披风脱掉
Lose the cape.
太老套了
It's a way too ninties-horror.
这是哪部电影的情节？
So what movie is this from?
啦啦队长之死？
Die Cheerleader, Die?
想演变态凶手？
Want to play psycho killer?
那我演无助的啦啦队长吧？
Can I be the helpless cheerleader?
那我该求你放过我罗？
So is this where I'm supposed to beg for my life?
求求你，凶手先生，别杀我
Please, Mr. Killer, don't kill me.
我该在这里流血？
So this is when I'm approved bleed?
看，我流血了
Oh, look, I'm bleeding.
我该逃了，对吧？
I'm supposed to run, right?
我在逃，我在逃了，救命
I'm running! I'm running! Help!
现在我该跌断腿，孤立无援
Now I'm going to fall and break my leg,leaving me helpless.
好了，凶手先生
There you go, Mr. Scary killer.
我很慌了
I'm panicking now.
天啊，快来人救救我
God, somebody please help me!
天啊，不
Oh, God, no.
现在呢？
Oh, now what?
我想这是全片高潮了
I guess this is the big climax.
希望你不会觉得我演太假了
Hope you don't mind if I fake it.
看看我
Oh, look at me.
我死了
I'm all dead.
我是颗恶心的头颅
I'm a gross, scary severed head.
拜托
Come on. Please.
知道是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
我是妙龄小姐
I'm Miss Teen.
你让我的头好痛
You're really giving me a headache.
你把我的古奇T恤染上血了
You got blood all over my Gucci sweater.
希望你会付出代价
I hope you're going to pay for that.
“失物招领”
LOST & FOUND
我要跳了
I'm going to jump!
菲尔
Phil!
回来
Get backing there!
不
No!
你在上面干嘛？
What are you doing up there?
理智点
Be reasonable.
我不要再教这些白烂学生了
I can't take this fucking job or those greasy shithead teenagers anymore!
我要结束这一切
I'm going to end it all!
等等
Wait! Hold on!
我们正在找人帮忙
We're getting help for you.
凶手不是巴比
Now we know Bobby's not the killer.
那是谁？
So who is?
不知道
I don't know.
昨晚凶手在你家为何不杀你？
If the killer was in your house last night,
他只想耍我们
why didn't he kill you then?
而他也的确达到目的了
Because he's just messing with us. Don't you see?
我们不能找警察
He's got us right where he wants us. We can't go to the police.
他正在等着我们
He's just out there... watching us and waiting for us.
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?!
你还等什么？
What are you waiting for?
What are you waiting for?!
我还等什么？
What am I waiting for?
What am I waiting for?!
你还等什么？
What are you waiting for?!
去你妈的
Fuck you!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
我还是不认为开派对是好主意
I still don't think this party is a good idea.
我会保护你的
You know I won't let nothing happen to you.
我只是觉得有危险
I just don't feel right.
我们为何不能做点别的？
Why can't we just do something else?
去看电影吧？
How about we go to the movies?
你喜欢看电影？
You like that?
我最喜欢这首歌
See a little movie? That is my song!
我还有机会在里面叫几声呢
You know they gave me a shout out on the album, right?
什么？
What?
没错
Yes.
不管走到哪，我都看到那贱人
Everywhere I go I see the same ho.
你穿我的运动衣很性感
Brenda.Did I tell you how sexy you look in my jersey?
真的？
I do, Ray?
没错
Yes.
我喜欢
I like it. Get up.
过来点，让我看看
Go over there. Let me see it.
继续
Go ahead.
好耶，我喜欢
Yes. I like that.
你喜欢？你喜欢？
You like that? You like that?
把这穿上
Put this on with it.
小雷，你真怪
Ray, you are so freaky.
没错
That's right.
我是大变态
You know I'm a freaky guy.
继续
Go on.
穿好
Pull it up, pull it up.
来
Here, here.
把这戴上
Put this on with it.
快啊
Go on.
你确定？
Are you sure?
快啊，戴上
Go on, girl, go on. Pull it on.
快啊
Go on.
我喜欢
I like that look.
我很坏的
I'm bad.
是啊
Ah, yes.
来，把这戴上
Here, put this on with it.
快啊，戴上它
Go on, girl. Put it on.
快，把那玩意戴上
Here. That shit on there. Come on.
用力戴
Just shove it on.
快戴啊
Do it.
好耶，真性感
Yeah. So fucking sexy.
过来
Come here, girl.
性感的小屁屁
Bring your little sexy ass here.
用力给我抱抱
Come on! Full speed, charge1
快啊，转过来
Yes! Come on! Turn around!
转过来
Turn around! Come on1
好耶，接招吧，布兰蛋
Yes, Brendan. Take it, Brendan.Take it, Brendan!
谁？
Who?
布兰妲，快，把安全帽戴上
Brenda. Come on, put the helmet on.
不，来玩角色扮演
No, let's role-play.
快，换你来上我
Come on. You get me. Get me. Come on.
我正在幽会停车场
I'm here at Lover's Lookout.
这里很黑，很偏僻
It's dark, it's in the middle of nowhere...
那些青少年就爱来这里爽
...and it's where hormone-driven teens love to come and fool around.
我们应该能看到有人被杀
So very likely we're about to see someone get killed.
那车里有个女孩
Sure enough, there's a girl in that car,
上衣松开
blouse unbuttoned, all alone.
看看她有没有话要说
Let's see if she'll have a word with us.
嗨，我是盖儿
Hi. Gail Hailstorm.
新书“下一个就是你”的作者
Author of the new book You're Next.
你叫什么名字？
Can you tell us your name?
希瑟
My name's Heather.
告诉我们你为何一个人在此？
Can you tell us what you're doing here all alone?
好，没问题
Well, yeah, sure.
我男友和我来这里玩耍
My boyfriend and I were just, like, making out...
接着我们听到声音
...and then we heard a noise,
他去查探
so he went to go check, but...
那是十分种前的事了
...that was, like, ten minutes ago.
你想他是不是遇害了...
Has it crossed your little mind that your boyfriend was probably murdered...
而你就是下一个？
...and you're about to be slaughtered next?
真的？不可能
Really? No way.
好，祝好运
Way. Good luck.
谢了，你真优秀
Thanks. You're the best.
我知道
I know.
正如我所想
Just as I thought.
凶手已经出现
The murder is happening as we speak!
我会设法拍下凶案过程，准备
I'll try and break into the bloodshed! Are you getting this?!
抱歉
Excuse me. Heather,
请问你现在感觉如何？
can you tell us what you're feeling,honey?
很痛
Lots of pain.
救救我
Gail, please help me!
Gail, please!
我很想救你
I'd like to help you,
但要先拼收视率
but it's sweeps.
先生，你有话要说吗？
Sir, can I get a word with you?
敢来这里算你勇敢
You got a lot of nerve coming here!
我只是扮演好我的角色
I'm just trying to do my job.
移开摄影机！
Get the camera off me right now!
继续拍
Keep rolling!
你死定了
You're dead, bitch.
我要跺下你的头
I'm going to slice your head off and shove it up his ass.
移开摄影机！
Get that camera off me!
快跑
Run!
天啊，肯尼
Oh, my God, Kenny!!
肯尼，把你的肥屁股移开点
Kenny, move your fat ass!
天啊，他就在身后
Oh, God ,he's right behind us!
这人正在追盖儿
Jeez, this man is chasing Gail!
我好害怕
I'm so scared right now.
我只想...
I just want to say.
对摄影师肯尼的家人说...
...to the family of my cameraman,
我很抱歉
Kenny... I am so sorry.
这是我的采访
This was my interview.
我的报导
My story.
一切都是我的错
It's all my fault.
“莎翁情史”
SHAKESPEARE IN LO VE
来点爆米花？
You want some popcorn?
我自己带了点零食来
I brought me a little snack of my own.
想吃炸鸡吗？
You want some chicken?
“请安静观赏”
PLEASE OBSERVE SILENCE
爱讲话的
For all y'all talkers up in here,
现在该闭上鸟嘴了
it's time to keep it down right now.
后面的安静点
Shh back at you.
干嘛？
Why they acting already?
现在还在放预告片啊
It nothing but the previews.
“预告限不成熟的观众看”
PREVIEW APPRO VED FOR MMATURE AUDIENCES ONLY
世上最大的一艘船
The largest ship the world had ever known.
四百名乘客和船员
Its four hundred passengers and crew
首航出发前往新世界
on a maiden voyage to a brave new world.
一趟永远改变他们命运的旅程
Ajourney that would change their lives forever.
我是世界之王
I'm the king of the world!
史蒂芬阿匹柏最新巨作
Steven Spilbug
“勇者无惧2”
AMISTAD II
快给我下来
Get your ass back down there, boy!
我要去上厕所
I'm going to the bathroom quick.
电影要开演了
The movie's about to come on!
我得上厕所
I got to go to the bathroom.
拿好你的辣酱
Here, take your hot sauce.
快点，别太久了
Hurry up, man. Don't be long.
让开，让他过去
Back up! Let him through!
往后坐一点
You can move back some.
戏院又不是你的
You don't own the theater.
“保证你当爸爸”
YOU'RE A D ADD Y C AN'T FEEL SHIT
开始了
And they're off.
二号紧跟在后
...number two close behind.
三号赢了
And number three is the winner.
二号紧接在后
Number two has placed,
四号第三
and number four to show.
下周比赛二点半开始
Next week's Triple Crown starts at Two-thirty.
要早点到
Be here early.
是谁啊？
Hey, who was that?
继续
Go ahead.
再来一次
Do it again, do it again.
我的天 别进去
Don't go in there!
我快休克了
Lord, I'm going to have a heartattack!
这真是吓人
Man, this is some scary shit!
我好害怕
Oh, I am scared!
抱歉
Excuse me.
我跟大家一样付钱进来的
I think I paid my money like everybody else up in here.
没人能管我
That ain't no man!
看的到她的真发呢
You can see her real hair right there!
拜托你
Do you mind?
你最好别来惹我
I know you better get out of my face!
别惹我
Out of my face!
滚开
我有权说话
This is all me up in here.
接受吧
You handle that!
你闭嘴好吗？
Will you shut the fuck up?!
这部片子真好看
This movie is good.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
你回来的正是时候
You came backjust in time.
布莱德彼特的前女友真怪
Brad Pitt's ex-girlfriend is a real freak.
她扮成男人...
She dressing like a man- -
闭嘴
Shut up.
我逮到你了
Yeah, I got you!
我录下你了
I got you on camera!
你被我录影存证了
You on Candid Camera now!
没想到吧
You ain't know that.
喂？
Hello?
我在看电影呢
Hey, girl. I'm in the movie.
莎翁情史
Shakespeare in love.
乱讲
You're lying!
天啊，闭上你的鸟嘴吧
For chrissake, just shut your trap!
闭嘴
Shut up!
等等
Hold on.
你们干嘛这样
I don't know why y'all is acting like this!
我朋友看过
My girlfriend saw the movie.
她说结局很烂
She said they don't stay together in the end.
把刀给我
Give me that.
好耶
Right on.
坐下好吗？
Will you sit down?!
闭嘴
Shut up!
臭婆娘
Your ass is grass.
我为女主角报仇
This is for Thelma!
还有男主角
And Louise!
谁叫你拼命讲话
This is for talking!
还有上一部片子
For The Fugitive!
你毁了“辛德勒的名单”
You ruined Schindler's List!
成龙的电影
Jackie Chan movie!
“不羁夜”
Boogie Nights!
还有“超级奶霸”
And Big Momma's House!
我不能娶罗拔的女儿
I cannot marry Sir Robert De Lesseps'daughter.
各位
You guys,
人数太多了...
there's a few too many people...
拜托，别吐
Honey, please don't throw up.
住手
Stop. Please!
那是我爸的，别碰...
That's my dad's! No don't touch- -
你还有啤酒吗？
Do you have more beer?
有，去车库找一找
Yeah. Check in the garage.
不，不
No. No!
“杀手撒旦牌”
Killer Satan Cult 45
猫咪，你吓到我了
Kitty, you scared me.
马儿
Horsey.
你也吓到我了
Oh, you scared me, too.
是谁？
Hello? Who's there?
天啊
Oh, my God.
不要
Oh, my God, please don't.
拜托，我只是临时演员
Please. I'm just a day player.
喝，喝，喝
Chug! Chug! Chug!
巴比
Bobby.
我好担心你
I was worried about you.
我以为凶手先找到你了
I thought the killer got to you before I could.
会吗？
Could what?
我想上楼
I want to go upstairs.
我想让你看点东西
There's something I want to show you.
继续玩吧
Hey, party on!
怎样...
So...
我们又在一起了
Here we are again.
你知道，如果你还没准备好
And you know, if you're not ready...
我能了解
...I'll understand.
我准备好了
I am ready.
真的？
You are?
对
Yeah.
我无法抵抗我的欲望
I can't keep fighting these urges.
我想放开一切
I have to just give in to them...
纵情享受
...and let them flow.
我一直都太自私了
I have been so selfish.
这好像某部电影的片段
This is like a scene from movie or something.
但这不是电影，巴比
Only it isn't a movie, Bobby.
这是真的
This is real life.
这是部电影
It's all a movie, baby.
收音师在那
There's the sound guy.
工作人员都在
There's the script supervisor.
你们好吗？
How you doing, baby?
干嘛？
What?
我指的是...
What I mean...
在真实生活中
...is that in real life,
你得享受一切
you have to enjoy each moment.
我能跟你讲个秘密吗？
Can I tell you a secret?
说吧
Sure, man.
我看得见鬼魂
I see dead people.
哇，这玩意炫呆了
Man, this shit is awesome!
你该多卷一点来抽
Yo, son, you got to roll some more of that shit!
但我们没烟纸了
Huh, son? But we don't have any more papers, man.
我们没烟纸了
We don't have any more papers.
我们可以用水管干嘛？
Oh, man. Now, what can we use to make a bong?
吸，吸吸
Toke, toke, toke.
妈的
Oh, shit, son.
这玩意酷毙了
This some good shit.
巴比
Bobby.
怎么？
What?
我没有做过
I've never done this before.
没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
那就像...
It's just like...
那就像在吃棒棒糖
It's like sucking on a Tootsie Roll Pop.
棒棒糖？
A Tootsie Pop?
对，樱桃口味的
Yeah. A cherry-flavor one.
中间有软糖的那种
With the fudge in the middle.
好耶，就是这样
Oh, yeah, just like that.
就是这样
Just like that, baby.
天啊
Oh! Jesus!
我每次都等不及就用咬的
I never could wait to get to the chewy middle.
让我来吧
You know what? Let me.
哇咧
Goddamn.
已经很久了
Guess it's been a while.
你的毛真劲爆
It's very seventies of you.
快，巴比，我要
Come here, Bobby! I want it now!
天啊，我爽呆了
Aw, man, am I fucking stoned.
我也是
Yeah, me too , son.
你们听见了吗？
Hey, you guys hear that?
喂？
Hello?
你好
Hello.
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
What's your favorite scary movie?
我要把你的内脏都挖出来
I'm going to gut you like a pig.
我是谁，巴比？
What's my name, Bobby?!
什么？
What?
我是谁，贱人
What's my name?! Bitch!
是辛蒂
God , it's Cindy!
谁最行，巴比？
Whose is it, Bobby?
Whose is it, Bobby?!
是你
It's yours.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
妈的
Oh, shit!!
别自己脱
Don't even contest
我会逼你脱
because I'll make you undress.
就像脱衣舞娘等着跳脱衣舞
Like porn dancers waiting at the front door for an answer.
我讨厌矽胶的大奶子
I'm sick of artificial MCs like silicone titties.
注意了
Hey, yo, check it. Fuck a cheap ball
我要去吸高品质的草
I'm going to smoke Cheech and Chong.
想要持久
If you want to fuck long,
我就吸更多
I'll let my ding-a-long hit the bong.
接着唱...
And then the song;
烟管一定要往左传
Always pass the dutchie to the left.
因为往右传是大错特错
Because the right way is wrong.
有了
I got one.
I got one, I got one.
我要唱了
Here is goes. Ready?
我要砍死，切死你
I'm going to slash and gash.
挖穿你屁屁
Cut another hole in your ass.
我要拿你的蛋蛋当球打
I spill blood on the walls then play tennis with your balls.
电话响了
If the phone rings,
可别接
don't answer the call.
切开你的喉咙，搞死你
Going to slit your throat. Fuck you like a goat.
剥了你的皮来做大衣
Peel your foreskin off and make a winter coat.
和平
Peace
这是我听过最棒的了
That was the illest rhyme I ever see, son!
你今晚本来在哪里？
Where were you tonight?
我只是好奇
I was just curious.
你怎么拖这么久才来？
What took you so long to get here?
你怎么这么好奇？
Why are you so curious?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以为会跟烂恐怖片一样...
I thought it would fit the nineties-horror clich.
结果你才是凶手
if...you turned out to be the killer.
你认为是我杀了帕妃和格瑞？
So wait.You think I killed Buffy and Gerg?
帕妃和格瑞死了？
Buffy and Greg are dead?
我以为你知道
I thought you knew that.
天啊
Oh, my God.
巴比，转过身去
Bobby, turn around!
是凶手
It's the killer!
天啊，巴比
Oh, my God. Bobby.
救救我
Help me.
宝贝，没事了
Bobby, it's okay.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
你不会有事的
It's going to be okay, Bob.
等等我
Yo, wait for me!
凶手在这里
There's a killer in the house!
到处都是血
There's ass, blood and guts everywhere!
有人发疯了
Someone done gone crazy, son!
我们多少都会发疯的
We all go a little crazy sometimes.
巴比，不
Bobby, no!!
妈的
Oh, shit, son!
我的天
Oh, my God.
他射中我胸口
They shot me in the lungs.
想吸一口吗？
You want to hit this shit?
蕃茄酱
Ketchup.
我妈做意大利面就只放这个
Just like my mom puts on her spaghetti, baby.
天啊，小雷
Oh, ma God, Ray.
你得帮我
You got to help me.
巴比疯了
Bobby's gone crazy!
惊喜
Surprise.
惊喜，辛蒂
Surprise, Cindy.
你为何这么做？
Why are you doing this, Bobby?
为什么？
Why?
听见吗
You hear that, Ray?
她要动机
I think she wants a motive.
“惊声尖叫”有什么剧情？
Did Scream have a plot?
没有
No.
“是谁搞的鬼”也烂毙了
Did I know What You Did Last Summer make any sense?
我不这么想
Don't think so.
续集里干嘛多了个牙买加白痴
And what was with that fat white Jamaican kid in the sequel?
我想杀了他
I want to kill that fucker.
我也是
Me too.
演员太烂了
It was bad casting, Bobby.
我觉得根本没激情场面
How about this for motive? Lack of sex!
那会导致变态行为
It can cause serious deviant behavior.
我以为你爱我
I thought you loved me.
我爱的
Oh, I did, baby.
I did.
但禁欲后能让你重新发掘自己
But abstinence can make you discover new things about yourself.
辛蒂，我是同志
That's right, Cindy. I'm gay.
万一你没注意
And in case you haven't noticed,
小雷也是
so is Ray.
什么？我才不是
What? I ain't gay.
那你为何带我到俱乐部去？
But you took me to that club.
那又怎样？那里音乐好听啊
So? They play good music.
去旧金山的事呢？
What about our trip to San Francisco?
我想去购物
I wanted to go shopping.
但你跟我做爱了
But you made love to me.
不，是你舔我弟弟
No. You sucked my dick.
我不想谈了
I don't want to talk about this now.
我要丢下一切
The point is... I'm a new man
开始新生
and I'm ready to leave all this behind and start a new life.
你要杀了你所有的朋友？
So you kill all your friends?
没有
Oh, no.
只有你
Just you.
还有矮子
And maybe Shorty,
但那不是预谋
but that wasn't planned or anything.
最天才的部份是...
But here's the genius part.
我们模仿真正的杀人凶手
We're copycatting a serial killer that already exists.
这是完全犯罪
It's the perfect crime.
等等，还有
But wait! There's more!
坐稳了
Hang on to your seat, baby.
这可有趣了
Because this one's a screamer!
我马上回来
I'll be back.
你快去...
Get your big ass...
爸
Dad!
你想干嘛？
What are you going to do?
诬陷他？
Frame him?
不，我们要玩玩你老爸
No. we're just having a little bit of fun with old daddio.
警方会发现你跟你爸都死了
The police are going to find you and Daddy both dead...
我和小雷是唯一的生还者
...and me and Ray the only survivors of a maniac's revenge.
准备好了？
You ready?
好了吗？我好了
You ready? I'm ready.
我好了，动手吧
I'm ready. Let's do this.
来吧
Come on.
好
All right.
快啊
Come.
快刺我
Give it to me.
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
好了？
Ready?
好了，等等
All right, wait.
动手吧
Let's do this. Come on.
好了，好了
Ready. Ready.
快，快刺我
Come on! Give it to me!
等等
Wait!
我们说好的
You remember what we talked about?
你要提几次？
How often will you go over it?
我知道的，别再提了
I know, okay? Stop. All right?
相信我，我知道我在干嘛
Trust me, okay? I got this shit. Ready?
等等
Wait!
等？我要割穿你喉咙了
What? I'm about to cut your throat!
别装了，快点
Stop acting like a little girl. Come on!
你说的对
You're right.
好了？
Ready?
我好了，来吧
I'm ready. Come on!
你们真变态
You guys are psychos!
你们看太多电视了
You've seen one too many TV shows!
不
No!
看电视节目不会造就变态杀手
Watching television shows doesn't create psycho killers!
取消电视节目才会
Canceling TV shows does!
吴宗宪的节目就超炫
The Wayans Brothers was a good-ass show, man!
我们连最后一集都没得录
And we didn't even get a final episode!
别刺我了
Take it easy.
我有点想吐了
I'm feeling a little woozy here.
该我了
It's my turn.
把刀给我
Give me the knife.
想都别想
Fuck out of here.
没人能拿刀砍我
Ain't nobody stabbing me.
惊喜，辛蒂
Surprise, Cindy.
很好
All right.
等等
Hold on a second.
我休息一下
Just give me a moment.
一下就好
One moment.
好了
Yeah. That's it.
可以了
All right. Okay.
爸
Dad.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
我说过我在家才能开派对的
I thought I told you not to have a party unless I was here.
你在啊
But you were here.
你在衣柜里
You were in the closet.
没错
Yeah, that's right.
帮我要到女生电话了？
Did you get some girlfriends' numbers for me?
她们都死了
Dad, they're dead.
我老是不走运
You know, I can't get a break.
那是什么？警察吗？
What's that? Is that the cops?
听着
Okay, listen, honey.
扶我起来
Help me up now.
告诉警察我是水电工
If the cops come, tell them I'm a plumber,okay?
你的水龙头坏了，我来修
You had a leaky faucet and they sent me over.
我们根本不认识
We don't even know each other.
不
No!!
爸，把手放下
Dad, get your arms down.
怎么回事？
What the hell's going on?
里面一片血海
It's a bloodbath in there.
他本来在这里，我发誓
He was right here! I swear!
谁？
Who was?
凶手
The killer!
那家伙杀光了我朋友
The guy that murdered all my friends!
那混蛋还在屋里藏毒品
And the sick bastard planted drugs in the house.
到处都是
All over the place.
爸，别说了
Dad. Stop it.
我得带你回警局
I'll have to take you down to the station.
我没事吧？
I'm cool, though, right?
I'm okay?
走吧，辛蒂
Let's go, Cindy.
打电话给我
Call me. Call me.
老爸会保你出来的
Daddy'll get you out.
再重头来过吧
Let's go over this again.
你说那是意外
You say it was an accident.
对
Yes.
他在路上
He was on the road.
你想他是回来报？
And you think he came back for revenge?
一定是他，警长
It has to be him, sheriff.
警长，他们要我把这交给你
Sheriff, they want me to get this to you.
好了，阿呆
That'll be all, Doofy.
我要走了
I'm going to go, then.
好
All right.
拜，辛蒂
Bye, Cind.
抱歉，辛蒂
I'm sorry, Cindy.
不是那个人
It wasn't the man you guys killed.
他叫奇大卫
His name was David Keegan.
一个渔夫发现他的尸体了
A fisherman found his body a few weeks later.
他被埋在湖林墓园
He's buried in Lakewood Cemetery.
不可能
That's impossible.
那我真的不知是谁了
Then I don't know who it could be.
一定是个知道所有事件的人
It's got to be someone connected to all the victims who knew about the accident.
一个不被人注意的人
Someone who could move around without being noticed.
我的天
Oh, my God.
她照顾过我弟阿呆
She used to babysit my brother, Doofy.
他爱她
He had the biggest crush on her.
是我，，辛蒂
It's me, Cind.
晚安，辛蒂
Night, Cind.
“阿呆”
DOOFUS PORCELAIN
阿呆
Doofy!
那个白痴？
Shithead?
有看到阿呆吗？
Have you seen Doofy?
没有
No.
有看到阿呆吗？
Have you seen Doofy?
没有
No, sheriff.
有人看到阿呆吗？
Has anybody seen Doofy?
没有
No.
他刚从后门走了，警长
Yeah, he just went out the back, sheriff.
不！
No!!
妈的，你好吗？
Shit, son. Yo, what the deal?
你们如果正在看这部片子
Yo, if y'all watching this tape right now...
那表示我没成功
...that means I didn't make it.
我不是被关，就是...
Either I'm a prisoner or worse.
死了
Dead.
不管怎样
But either way it goes.
我要告诉各位生存法则
I tell you all the rules to survive this situation.
第一，动作要快
Rule number one; You got to be quick.
第二，别跌倒
Rule number two; Don't fall down.
第三...
And rule number three;
无论如何都别回头看
Whatever you do, never look back.
祝我好运吧
Y'all wish me luck.
拿了就跑啊
Snatch and run, y'all!
回来，混蛋
Come back here, you motherfuckers!
痞子
Son of a bitch!
谨献给海伦马汀和雪莉汉菲
THIS FILM IS DEDIC ATED TO HELEN MARTIN & SHIRLEY HEMPHIL